<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="typecobol.editor.feature"
      label="TypeCobol Editor Feature"
      version="1.0.0">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      [Enter Feature Description here.]
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      [Enter Copyright Description here.]
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      The code of this repository is published under the CeCILL-C v1 Open Source Licence, which is very similar to the LGPL but was adapted to be compatible with the french law.

http://www.cecill.info/licences/Licence_CeCILL-C_V1-en.html

Summary :

    The Licensee is authorized to use the Software, without any limitation as to its fields of application.

    The Licensee acknowledges that the Software is supplied &quot;as is&quot; by the Licensor without any other express or tacit warranty.

    DISTRIBUTION OF SOFTWARE WITHOUT MODIFICATION : The Licensee is authorized to distribute true copies of the Software in Source Code or Object Code form, provided that said distribution complies with all the provisions of the Agreement and is accompanied by: 1.a copy of the Agreement, 2.a notice relating to the limitation of both the Licensor&apos;s warranty and liability as set forth in Articles 8 and 9, and 3.the Licensee allows effective access to the full Source Code of the Software.

    DISTRIBUTION OF MODIFIED SOFTWARE : The Licensee is authorized to distribute the Modified Software, in source code or object code form, provided that said distribution complies with all the provisions of the Agreement and is accompanied by: 1.a copy of the Agreement, 2.a notice relating to the limitation of both the Licensor&apos;s warranty and liability as set forth in Articles 8 and 9, and 3.the Licensee allows effective access to the full source code of the Modified Software.

    DISTRIBUTION OF DERIVATIVE SOFTWARE : When the Licensee creates Derivative Software, this Derivative Software may be distributed under a license agreement other than this Agreement, subject to compliance with the requirement to include a notice concerning the rights over the Software.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="typecobol.editors.eclipse"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
